actressphoto.org 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy - Actressphoto.org

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of Actressphoto.org.

Actressphoto.org will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on Actressphoto.org.

Actressphoto.org does not use affiliate links on the site and request that you notify us immediately if you come across any.

Actressphoto.org uses Google Adsense to display advertisement and Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to Actressphoto.org users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Actressphoto.org is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.

A “cookie” is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows Actressphoto.org to recognize you each time you visit this site (customization etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and Actressphoto.org does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds.

While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to Actressphoto.org and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Actressphoto.org have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions.

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.

For any other information, please email the founder, at __
